Guide to the Wade Hall 8 track tapes PM.012
University Libraries Division of Special Collections, The University of Alabama
Wade Hall 8 track tapes
1965-1980s
PM.012
University Libraries Division of Special Collections, The University of Alabama
40.0 boxes
A collection of Wade Hall's music, featuring a variety of genres, but with a focus on country music.
General note
To provide faster access to our materials, this finding aid was published without formal and final review. Email us at archives@ua.edu if you find mistakes or have suggestions to make this finding aid more useful for your research.
Provenance
Gift of Wade Hall
Hall, Wade, 1934-; Audiotapes
- Box 1
  - Heaven's Sounding Sweeter All the Time - featuring Jimmy Swaggart with Dwain Johnson and the Phil Johnson Singers - Baton Rouge, La.: Jim Records, 1976. (Jim 125) (Box 1)
  - Home by Loretta Lynn - MCA Records, 1975. (MCAT-2146) (Box 1)
  - Genius Live in Concert - Ray Charles - ABC Records, 1973. (M 8051-6053) (Box 1)
  - Sweet Baby James - by James Taylor - Warner Bros. no date (M81843), n.d. (Box 1)
  - When Will I See You Again - Johnny Mathis - CBS Inc. & John Mat Records, 1975. (PCA 33420) (Box 1)
  - Alone Again - George Jones - CBS Inc., 1976. (EA34290) (Box 1)
  - Greatest Hits by the Sandpipers - A & M Records, no date. (8T-4246) (Box 1)
  - Visions of a New World - Lonnie Liston Smith & the Cosmic Echoes - NY: Flying Dutchman & RCA Records, 1975. (BDS1-1196) (Box 1)
  - Country Feeling - Porter Wagoner - RCA, no date. (C8S 1078), n.d. (Box 1)
  - 24 Greatest Hits vol. 2 - Hank Williams, Sr. - MGM Records, 1977. (8T2 5401) (Box 1)
  - A Very Merry Christmas, vol. 5 - W.T. Grant - RCA, 1971. (PC8S-582) (Box 1)
  - Rock 1980 by various artists - Hollywood, CA: 4-Star Music, 1980? (R819) (Box 1)
  - Broadway - My Way by Nancy Wilson - Capitol Records, no date. (8XY-4575), n.d. (Box 1)
  - 10th Anniversary of Golden Piano Hits, vol. 2 - Ferrante & Teicher - Los Angeles: Liberty/United Artists, no date. (U8164), n.d. (Box 1)
  - Little Criminals - Randy Newman - Warner Bros., 1977. (M8-3079) (Box 1)
  - Best of Eddy Arnold - no information, n.d. (Box 1)
  - I Want to Go With You - Eddy Arnold - RCA, no date. (P8S 1119), n.d. (Box 1)
- Box 2
  - Country Sunshine: featuring the velvet memories of Jim Reeves - part of the Country Music Cavalcade series - RCA Records, 1978., 2.0 items (Box 2)
  - Midnight in Memphis pt. 1 & 2 - part of the Country Music Cavalcade series - MGM, Mercury Records, 1975., 2.0 items (Box 2)
  - Country Guitar & Piano: featuring Chet Atkins and Floyd Cramer - part of the Country Music Cavalcade series - RCA Records,1976., 2.0 items (Box 2)
  - Love in the Country: the magic touch of Eddy Arnold - part of the Country Music Cavalcade series - MGM, Candlelite Music, 1977., 2.0 items (Box 2)
  - From Music City with Love - part of the Country Music Cavalcade series - Candlelite, 1980., 2.0 items (Box 2)
  - Jamboree: featuring the legendary magic of Hank Williams - part of the Country Music Cavalcade series - Candlelite Music, 1980., 2.0 items (Box 2)
  - For the Good Times - part of the Country Music Cavalcade series - RCA Records, 1977., 2.0 items (Box 2)
  - Nashville Graffitti - part of the Country Music Cavalcade series - Candlelite Music, 1976., 2.0 items (Box 2)
- Box 3
  - Memory Lane pt 1 & 2: featuring Truck Drivers and other American Heroes - part of the Country Music Cavalcade series - Candlelite Music, 1980. (no box), 2.0 items (Box 3)
  - American Country Gold - part of the Country Music Cavalcade series - Candlelite Music, 1980. (only pt. 2), 1.0 item (Box 3)
  - Nashville Scrapbook - part of the Country Music Cavalcade series - Candlelite Music, 1977. (pt 2 only), 1.0 item (Box 3)
  - The Legend & the Music of Johnny Cash & Friends - part of the Country Music Cavalcade series - Candlelite Music, 1977. (pt 2 only), 1.0 item (Box 3)
  - Twilight in Tennessee: sweet southern sounds - part of the Country Music Cavalcade series - Candlelite Music, 1977. (pt 2 only), 1.0 item (Box 3)
  - Country Music, U.S.A. - part of Country Music Cavalcade - box only, n.d.; 1.0 item (Box 3)
  - Tom T. Hall Greatest Hits, vol. 2 - Mercury Records, 1975. (MC8 1-1044) (S 114450) (Box 3)
  - Santana's Greatest Hits - CBS, Inc., 1974. (PCA 33050) (Box 3)
  - Hits made famous by George Jones and Tammy Wynette - Jacksonville, FL: Eagle Music, 1977. (E-1387). (Box 3)
  - "Dr. Fountain's Magical Licorice Stick Remedy for the Blues" - Pete Fountain - New York: Coral Records/MCA, no date. (6-57513), n.d. (Box 3)
  - Best of Ernest Tubb- Gannaway Productions, 1973. (C-639-L) (Box 3)
  - It Was Almost Like a Song - Ronnie Milsap - RCA, 1977. (APS1-2439) (Box 3)
  - This Is Me - Barbara Fairchild - CBS Inc., 1978. (CA 35536) (Box 3)
  - Ol' T's In Town - Tom T. Hall - RCA, 1979. (AHS1-3495) (Box 3)
- Box 4
  - A Sure Thing - Freddie Hart - Newport Beach, CA: Sunbird Records, no date. (8XT-50100), n.d. (Box 4)
  - Greatest Hits - George Jones & Tammy Wynette - CBS Inc., 1977. (EA 34716) (Box 4)
  - Chosen - The Goodmans - Canaan Records, 1982. (3-9899) (slipcase "HeartWarming") (Box 4)
  - "Home" - Loretta Lynn - no date. (C-2728), n.d. (Box 4)
  - Country Songs of Tennessee - Cowboy Copas - Altone, no date. (512-0416), n.d. (Box 4)
  - Willie Nelson's Greatest Hits (and some that will be) - Columbia/CBS, 1981. (K2A 37542) (Box 4)
  - Did you think to pray - Charley Pride - RCA, 1971. (P8S-1723) (Box 4)
  - In the name of love - Peggy Lee - Capitol, no date. (8XY-4618), n.d. (Box 4)
  - Piano favorites - Liberace - Rahway, NJ: Springboard Records, no date. (8T-SPB-4013), n.d. (Box 4)
  - Greats of Roy Clark & Buck Owens - no date. (C-409), n.d. (Box 4)
  - Feels So Right - Alabama - RCA, 1981. (AHS1-3930) (Box 4)
  - Best of the Statler Brothers - Mercury, 1975. (MC8-1-1037) (Box 4)
  - Moody Blue - Elvis - RCA, 1977. (AFS1-2428) (Box 4)
  - Best of Dolly Parton - RCA, 1975. (APS1-1117) (Box 4)
  - Rolling Stones Greatest Hits - vol. 1 - ABKCO, 1977. (TA8-1088) (Box 4)
  - Hank Williams, Jr.'s Greatest Hits, vol. 2 - no date. (554)., n.d. (Box 4)
  - Mel Tillis and Friends - Gusto Records, 1977. (PO-1295) (Box 4)
- Box 5
  - Blues is my middle name - Ray Charles - Altone, no date. (1134), n.d. (Box 5)
  - All my best - Loretta Lynn -Tee Vee Records, 1978. (MST-35011) (TA8-2008) (Box 5)
  - Let It Be - The Beatles - no date. (ART 8001), n.d. (Box 5)
  - Southern Fried Rock - Minnetonka, MN: K-tel, 1980. (NU 9528) (Box 5)
  - Mancini Country: Henry Mancini, his piano, orchestra, & chorus - no date. (230), n.d. (Box 5)
  - Nashville Gold - Columbia, no date. (CA 10179) "Limited Edition - Not for Resale", n.d. (Box 5)
  - World's Favorite Piano Music - Van Cliburn - RCA, 1972. (R8S-1303). (Box 5)
  - Tom Jones Live in Las Vegas - Parrot, no date. (PEM 79831), n.d. (Box 5)
  - Lily Tomlin: This is a recording - Polydor, no date. (8F 4055)., n.d. (Box 5)
  - Get Together - The Young Lovers - no date. (P8-1119), n.d. (Box 5)
  - Sunny Tennessee - Cowboy Copas. George Jones, Buck Owens & Others - Country Road, no date. (CR 8T 32), n.d. (Box 5)
  - We'll Sing in the Sunshine - Helen Reddy - Capitol Records, 1978. (S 120079) (Box 5)
  - Gentle on my mind - Columbia Musical Treasury Orchestra and Chorus - no date. (VS-118-8-TQ) (Box 5)
  - The Twain Shall Meet - Eric Burdon and the Animals - MGM, no date. (MCB 84537) (Box 5)
  - Orange Blossom Special - Lewis Kappell - Just Jammin' - no date., n.d. (Box 5)
  - New Orleans - Anthony Armstrong, J. Jones - Vivid Country Sounds, no date. (VCS-509-8T-Q) (Box 5)
  - I Can Help - Billy Swan - Soul, no date. (S-431), n.d. (Box 5)
- Box 6
  - Remember Me - T. Texas Tyler - Nashville, no date. (N8-2106), n.d. (Box 6)
  - Sophisticated Lady and other thrilling selections by Duke Ellington - CMC, no date. (8108) (Box 6)
  - Black Oak Arkansas - Street Party - no date. (1464), n.d. (Box 6)
  - Leapin - Charlie Barnet - CMC, no date. (8103), n.d. (Box 6)
  - Chet Atkins a legendary performer vol. 1 - RCA, 1977. (CPS1-2503) (Box 6)
  - Completely Well - B.B. King - no date. (937), n.d. (Box 6)
  - Freedom Suite vol. 2 - The Rascals - no date. (ALM 82901), n.d. (Box 6)
  - Catch the Wind - Donovan - Hickory, no date. (172-123) (Box 6)
  - Mancini Country - Henry Mancini - TCA, no date. (#HM-352), n.d. (Box 6)
  - Better Take a Mouth Organ - Danny Welton's Mouth Organ & Orchestra - CMC, no date. (8113) (Box 6)
  - Soul 36 - various artists- no date. (1741), n.d. (Box 6)
  - The Cugat Touch - Xavier Cugat - Springboard, no date. (8T-SPB-4060), n.d. (Box 6)
  - Bonology - Herbie Breen and the Velvet Trombones- Universal, no date. (U8-107) (Box 6)
  - The Soul of Spain - 101 Strings - no date. (ASX 85018), n.d. (Box 6)
  - Super Hits 1975 vol. 3 - Gusto Records, 1975. (SA-1267), n.d. (Box 6)
  - Carryin' On - with Johnny Cash & June Carter - Columbia, no date. (18 10 0270), n.d. (Box 6)
  - Super Hits '74 vol. 3 - Country - various artists - Gusto Records, 1974. (SA 1262) (Box 6)
- Box 7
  - Miami - The James Gang - Right on Rock, no date. (5031), n.d. (Box 7)
  - Soft Vibes, Soaring Strings - Lionel Hampton - Vivid Sounds, no date. (VS-129-8-TQ) (Box 7)
  - Jimmie Davis' Greatest Hits - MCA Records, no date. (MCAT-269), n.d. (Box 7)
  - Totally Free - Dale Evans - Word Inc., 1979. (2B-8803) (Box 7)
  - Up Up and Away - The Generation Gap - Riviera, no date. (R8-54) (Box 7)
  - "Jermaine" - Jermaine Jackson - Motown, 1972. (M752T) (Box 7)
  - 101 Strings play hits made famous by The Crooners - no date. (ASX 85110), n.d. (Box 7)
  - Nelson Riddle and the 101 Strings - 1970. (E 85203) (Box 7)
  - Maybe Tomorrow - Jackson Five - no date. (636), n.d. (Box 7)
  - Damita Jo live at Basin Street East - Vivid Sounds, no date. (VS-140-8-TQ) (Box 7)
  - Smile - Larry Gatlin & the Gatlin Brothers - CBS/Columbia, 1985. (FCA 40068) (Box 7)
  - Pop Parade - Hugo Winterhalter and his orchestra - Skokie, IL: Musico Stereo Records, no date. (8T-MDS-1013) (Box 7)
  - Mighty Clouds of Joy - Miracle Man - Word, Inc., 1982. (Myrrh 6B-6694) (Box 7)
  - That Christmas Feeling - Bing Crosby - MCA Records, 1976. (MCAT-15019) (Box 7)
  - Seven Separate Fools - Three Dog Night - ABC/Dunhill Records, 1972. (50118-8) (Box 7)
  - Bud Shank with Maynard Ferguson, Stu Williamson, and Bob Enevoldson - Vogue, no date. (V8-104) (Box 7)
  - Someone to Care - Jimmy Swaggart - no date. (G-302), n.d. (Box 7)
- Box 8
  - Amertone tape head cleaning cartridge - beep tone, n.d. (Box 8)
  - Hot Trumpets - Ray McKenzie and his orchestra - Cassette Music, no date. (8102) (Box 8)
  - Early in the Morning - George Beverly Shea - arranged by Bill Walker - produced by Kurt Kaiser - Word, Inc., 1979. (2B-8830) (Box 8)
  - Best of the Imperials no date, n.d. (Box 8)
  - I'm Tore Up - Billy "Crash" Craddock - Gusto Records, 1975. (PO 1281) (Box 8)
  - Al Hirt & Slide Hampton in New Orleans - no date. (Altone 1020), n.d. (Box 8)
  - I Want to Live - John Denver - RCA, 1977. (AFS1-2521) (Box 8)
  - Patsy Cline's Greatest Hits - MCA, no date. ( MCAT-12) (6-4854), n.d. (Box 8)
  - The Last Word in Lonesome - Eddy Arnold - RCA, 1966. (DRS1-0040) (Box 8)
  - Louvin Brothers - their great gospel singing - Akron, OH: Sunshine Sales, no date. (30), n.d. (Box 8)
  - Impossible Dream - Ed Ames - RCA, no date. (P8S 1454), n.d. (Box 8)
  - Porgy & Bess - Ray Charles and Cleo Laine - RCA, no date. (CPS2-1831) (Box 8)
  - Special Delivery - Doug Oldham - Impact, 1979. (T3546C) (Box 8)
  - Super Hits 1975 vol. 2 - Gusto Records, 1975. (SA-1266) (Box 8)
  - A Tribute to Stevie Wonder - Audio Central Tunes, 1974. (Box 8)
  - More or Less McCann - Les McCann - Liberty, no date. (8997), n.d. (Box 8)
  - Pure Gold - Peter Nero - RCA, 1976. (ANS1-1592) (Box 8)
- Box 9
  - Jimmy Dorsey's Greatest Hits - Jimmy Dorsey and his orchestra - no date. (P-3) (Box 9)
  - Mason Williams Ear Show - Warner Bros. - no date. (8WM-1766), n.d. (Box 9)
  - Here's Johnny...Magic Moments from the Tonight Show - Johnny Carson - Casablanca, 1974. (CAB 1296-1 part 1) (Box 9)
  - Stereo Brass - Ray McKenzie and his orchestra - Cassette Music, no date. (CMC 8105) (Box 9)
  - Freedom Suite vol. 1 - The Rascals -Atlantic, no date. (ALM 81901), n.d. (Box 9)
  - Keating Straight Ahead - The Keating Sound - London Records, no date. (LEM 14072) (Box 9)
  - Partridge Family Album - no date. (M 86050), n.d. (Box 9)
  - Leroy Anderson's Best - no date. (LP8S-315) (Box 9)
  - Miles Davis - Radiant, no date. (512-1004), n.d. (Box 9)
  - Lookin Through the Windows - The Jackson 5 - Motown, 1972. (MOT M 8750) (Box 9)
  - Around the World in Percussion - Billy Mure - no date. (P 19) (Box 9)
  - Once Upon a Time - Kingston Trio - Orbit, no date. (8T-ORB-7021), n.d. (Box 9)
  - Super Hits of Atlantic Recording Stars - no date. (L-96-501), n.d. (Box 9)
  - Playback of the Monkees and the Beatles - Allan Gray and his orchestra - Cassette Music, no date. (8118) (Box 9)
  - Buddy and Soul - Buddy Rich Big Band - Liberty/UA, no date. (8 8964) (Box 9)
  - Hawaiian Paradise with Billy Mure - Altone, no date. (1055), n.d. (Box 9)
  - Merry Christmas - Brenda Lee - MCA, no date. (MCAT-15021) (Box 9)
- Box 10
  - Nobody's Blues But Mine vol. 1 - Bessie Smith - no date. (580), n.d.; 2.0 (Box 10)
  - Simple Dreams - Linda Ronstadt - Elektra/Asylum Records, 1977. (ET-8104) (Box 10)
  - Love Letters - Engelbert Humperdinck - London, 1978. (PS8 709) (Box 10)
  - Best of BTO (So Far) - Bachman-Turner Overdrive - Phonogram, 1975. (MC 8 1-1101) (Box 10)
  - Sessions presents 40 original hits - RCA, 1976. (DPS2-0171 P1), 2.0 (Box 10)
  - After Dark - Andy Gibb - RSO Records, 1980. (8T-1-3069) (Box 10)
  - Cruisin' - Village People - Casablanca/RCA, no date. (S 124276) (Box 10)
  - Love Gun - Kiss - Casablanca, 1977. (CAF 87057) (Box 10)
  - Life for the Taking - Eddie Money - CBS, 1978. (JCA 35598) (Box 10)
  - Blondes Have More Fun - Rod Stewart - Warner Bros./WEA Records, 1978. (Box 10)
  - Leaders of the Pack - Brookville Records, 1974. (8500-8001) (Box 10)
  - Country-Pop Hits of the '70's vol. 6 - Capitol Records, 1979. (51-6067) (Box 10)
  - Best of Merle Haggard - no date. (OS 22), n.d. (Box 10)
  - The Swarm original motion picture soundtrack - Warner Bros, 1978. (Box 10)
  - Elvis Presley - Double Dynamite - Pickwick, 1975. (D82-5001) (Box 10)
- Box 11
  - I Reserve the Right - Stillwater - Capricorn Records, 1978. (M8N-0210) (Box 11)
  - Best of Barbara Mandrell - ABC Records, 1979. (802-1119) (Box 11)
  - Country Pac '74 - various artists - ABC, 1974. (Box 11)
  - Help Me Make It Through the Night and other big hits - Sammi Smith - Gambit, no date. (G-508) (Box 11)
  - Elvis' Worldwide Gold Award Hits - parts 1 & 2 - RCA, 1974. (S 213690), 2.0 (Box 11)
  - I Don't Want to Have to Marry You - Jim Ed Brown/Helen Cornelius - RCA, 1976. (APS1-2024) (Box 11)
  - Nicolette - Nicolette Larson - Warner Bros, 1978. (WB M8 3243) (Box 11)
  - Rock, Roll & Remember - Dick Clark - CBS, 1984. (Box 11)
  - Feels So Good - Chuch Mangione - A & M Records, 1977. (8T 4658) (Box 11)
  - Stranger in Town - Bob Seger & the Silver Bullet Band - Capitol, 1978. (8XW 11698) (Box 11)
  - Four & More - Miles Davis - no date. (178), n.d. (Box 11)
  - Waylon "Live" - Waylon Jennings - RCA, 1974. (APS1-1108) (Box 11)
  - Dark Lady - Cher - MCA, 1974. (MCAT - 2113) (Box 11)
  - Superstars of the 70's (tape 1) - Warner, 1973. (4000-1) (Box 11)
  - Evolution - Journey - CBS, 1979. (35797) (Box 11)
  - Transition - Kenny Rogers and the First Edition - no date. (M 82039) (Box 11)
- Box 12
  - Nashville - Music City, U.S.A. - Super Gold Country 101 - no date., n.d. (Box 12)
  - Oak Ridge Boys Christmas - MCA, 1982. (S143744) (Box 12)
  - Dick Clark - Rock, Roll & Remember - CBS, 1984. (Box 12)
  - Back in Black - AC DC - Atlantic, 1980. (TP 16018) (Box 12)
  - Crumbs From the Table - The Echoes of Faith - no date., n.d. (Box 12)
  - Can't Stop Dancing - by Dynamic Sound - T.E.J. Records, 1977. (TEJ #2005) (Box 12)
  - Classic Instrumentals - Hank Williams' Original Drifting Cowboys Band - Delta Records, 1981.(D8T - 1114) (Box 12)
  - Carolina Dreams - The Marshall Tucker Band - Capricorn Records, 1977. (M8-0180) (Box 12)
  - To All My Wonderful Fans From Me to You - Charley Pride - RCA, 1971. (P8S-1662) (Box 12)
  - The Nashville Sound: Bright Lights and Country Music vols. 5 & 6 - CBS, 1973. (Box 12)
  - Oak Ridge Boys - Gusto Records, 1978. (SLPT-1356) (Box 12)
  - Johnny Rivers' Greatest Hits - Imperial House, 1981. (NU 9578) (Box 12)
  - Chipmunk Rock - The Chipmunks - RCA, 1982. (AFS1-4304) (Box 12)
  - Convoy - various artists - Fantastic -F Inc., 1975. (H-1005) (Box 12)
  - Dynamic Duo - Conway Twitty/Loretta Lynn - MCA, 1977. (MCT 2278) (Box 12)
  - Rhinestone Cowboy - Glen Campbell - no date., n.d. (Box 12)
  - Go West - Village People - Casablanca, 1979. (NBL8-7144) (Box 12)
- Box 13
  - Elvis: A Legendary Performer vol. 1 - RCA, 1973. (CPS1-0341) (Box 13)
  - Elvis - Twin set - RCA, 1973. (Box 13)
  - Here Where There Is Love - Dionne Warwick - Scepter Records, no date. (91-555), n.d. (Box 13)
  - Golf Game & Other Funnys - Jeb & Cousin Easy - no date. (#101), n.d. (Box 13)
  - Melodies of Love - Bobby Vinton - ABC Records, 1974. (S 113334) (Box 13)
  - One Man Dog - James Taylor - Warner Bros., 1972. (M8 2660) (Box 13)
  - King of the Road - Boxcar Willie - SMI, 1980. (SMI 8-24A) (Box 13)
  - There Goes My Heart - Ronnie Milsap - CBS, 1979. (QA 16026) (Box 13)
  - Best of the Statler Brothers - Mercury, 1975. (MC8-1-1037) (Box 13)
  - Original Gold - part 2 - RCA, 1975. (DPS2-0142-P2) (Box 13)
  - Leaders of the Pack - Brookville Records, 1974. (8500-8001) (Box 13)
  - You're Gonna Get It - Tom Petty and the Heartbreakers - Shelter Records, 1978. (DA 52029 H) (Box 13)
  - Joy to the World/Their Greatest Hits - Three Dog Night - ABC/Dunhill, 1974. (8023) (Box 13)
  - Flowing Rivers - Andy Gibb - RSO Records, 1977. (8T-1-3019) (Box 13)
  - Happy Harmonica - The Great Harmonica Hits - GRT, 1976. (309 ST) (Box 13)
  - Root Boy Slim & the Sex Change Band with the Rootettes - Warner Bros., 1978., 2.0 (Box 13)
- Box 14
  - Four & More - Miles Davis - no date. (178), n.d. (Box 14)
  - Out Where the Bright Lights Are Glowing - Ronnie Milsap - RCA, 1981. (AAS1-3932) (Box 14)
  - Someone Loves You Honey - Charley Pride - RCA, 1978. (APS1-2478) (Box 14)
  - Bert Kaempfert Now! - Decca, no date. (5305), n.d. (Box 14)
  - Lynyrd Skynyrd - MCA, 1973. (MCAT-363) (Box 14)
  - Anthology vol. II - Marvin Gaye - Motown, 1973. (M-791-ZT) (Box 14)
  - The Tubes - What Do You Want From Live - A & M Records, 1978. (8T-6003) (Box 14)
  - I Love a Piano - tape 3 - Reader's Digest, 1977. (RD5A-024-1/3) (Box 14)
  - Chick Corea, Herbie Hancock, Keith Jarrett, McCoy Tyner - Atlantic, 1976. (TP 1696) (Box 14)
  - Gene Tracy no. 5 in England - Party, no date. (P-521) (Box 14)
  - Skylark - Freddie Hubbard - ABC Records, 1978. (Q8J-25163) (Box 14)
  - Some Girls - The Rolling Stones - Warner, 1978. (TP 39108) (Box 14)
  - The Originials - The Statler Brothers - Mercury, 1979. (MC8-1 5016) (Box 14)
  - Brass on Ivory - Mancini/Severinsen - RCA, 1972. (P8S-1862) (Box 14)
  - Johnny Rivers - no information. (358), n.d. (Box 14)
  - Dave Clark Five Greatest Hits - Lyric Sounds, no date. (R-1027) (Box 14)
  - Honky Chateau - Elton John - This Record Co., 1972. (UN8 93135) (Box 14)
- Box 15
  - Disco Dynamos - CBS Records, 1979. (PA-15116) (Box 15)
  - Best of Mel Tillis and the Statesiders - MGM, 1975. (8T1 5021) (Box 15)
  - Indianola Mississippi Seeds - B.B. King - no date. (Box 15)
  - Hotter Than July - Stevie Wonder - Motown, 1980. (T8 373 KT) (Box 15)
  - Pickin' My Way - Chet Atkins - no date. (286), n.d. (Box 15)
  - Greatest Hits - Country Joe & the Fish - Vanguard, no date. (M 86545), n.d. (Box 15)
  - Say You'll Stay Until Tomorrow - Tom Jones - CBS, 1977. (PEA 34468) (Box 15)
  - Anthology vol. I - Marvin Gaye - Motown, 1973. (M-791ZT) (Box 15)
  - Bee Gees Gold vol. 1 - RSO Records, 1976. (8T-1-3006) (Box 15)
  - Amazing Love - Charley Pride - RCA, 1973. (PS1-0397) (Box 15)
  - Briefcase Full of Blues - Blues Brothers - Atlantic, 1978. (TP 19217) (Box 15)
  - The Rose - original soundtrack recording - Atlantic, 1979. (TP 16010) (Box 15)
  - Hag - Merle Haggard and the Strangers - Capitol Records, no date. (8XT-735) (Box 15)
  - Straight Shooter - Bad Company - no date. (1913), n.d. (Box 15)
  - Who's Gonna Play This Old Piano - Jerry Lee Lewis - Mercury, 1972. (MC 8-61366) (Box 15)
  - Sooner or Later - Rex Smith - CBS, 1979. (JCA 35813) (Box 15)
  - The Sound of Love - Liberace - Paramount, no date. (PA81100) (Box 15)
- Box 16
  - Space - George Benson - Citi Records, 1978. (CT8 7085) (Box 16)
  - Soul! The Best of Otis Redding - no date., n.d. (Box 16)
  - I Am What I Am - George Jones - CBS, 1980. (36586) (Box 16)
  - Tom Jones' Greatest Hits - London Records, 1973. (RCA Music Club Edition) (M 79862) (Box 16)
  - Fandango - ZZ Top - London Records, 1975. (LON 0 8656) (Box 16)
  - I Love You So - Natalie Cole - Capitol, 1979. (8XO 11928) (Box 16)
  - Hold It! - Bill Doggett - Power Pak, no date. (PO-1269), n.d. (Box 16)
  - Original movie soundtrack Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band - RSO Records, 1978. (entire record set 1598) (8T-2-4100) (Box 16)
  - Entertainers ... On and Off the Record - The Statler Brothers - Mercury, 1978. (MC 8 1-5007) (Box 16)
  - Anthology vol. 1 - Diana Ross & The Supremes - Motown, 1974. (M-11-794-NT vol. 1) (Box 16)
  - Stardust - Willie Nelson - CBS, 1978. (JCA 35305) (Box 16)
  - Fancy Free - Oak Ridge Boys - MCA, 1979. (MCAT 5209) (Box 16)
  - Very Best of the Statler Brothers - Realm Records, 1977. (1A2 8077) (Box 16)
  - East Bound and Down - Jerry Reed - RCA, 197? (APS1-2516) (Box 16)
  - Sarah Vaughan's Greatest Hits - Radiant, no date. ( 512-0301), n.d. (Box 16)
  - Disney Songs the Stachmo Way - Louis Armstrong - Buena Vista, no date. (P8BV 1001), n.d. (Box 16)
  - Mel's Favorites - Mel Tillis - TeeVee/MCA, 1979. (TV8-1040) (Box 16)
- Box 17
  - Aloha from Hawaii via satellite - Elvis Presley - RCA, 1973. (P8S-5144) (Box 17)
  - Souled - Jose Feliciano - RCA, no date. (P8S-1381), n.d. (Box 17)
  - Chet Atkins Picks on the Beatles - RCA, no date. (P8S-1103), n.d. (Box 17)
  - Boots Randolph - home recording? (Box 17)
  - All Things In Time - Lou Rawls - CBS, 1976. (PZA 33957) (Box 17)
  - Very Best of Loretta and Conway - MCA, 1979. (MCAT-3164) (Box 17)
  - Some Girls - The Rolling Stones - 1978. (TP 39108) (Box 17)
  - Surfin' Safari - The Beach Boys - Capitol, no date. (8XY-4572), n.d. (Box 17)
  - Best of Freddy Fender - ABC, 1977. (S 114013) (Box 17)
  - Hollywood Be Thy Name - Dr. John - United Artist, 1975. (handwritten label) (Box 17)
  - Luau Special - hand written label - no date. (Box 17)
  - Lucille - B.B. King - no date. (no. 244), n.d. (Box 17)
  - Mickey's Movin' On - Mickey Gilley - Playboy Records, 1975. (PBT 405) (Box 17)
  - Just Sittin' Here Singin' - Jimmy Reed - no date. (8T 0014), n.d. (Box 17)
  - Waylon and Willie - Waylon Jennings and Willie Nelson - RCA, 1978. (AFS1-2686) (Box 17)
  - Liberace and the Warner Brothers Symphony Orchestra play Rhapsody in Blue- CBS, 1976. (BA 13567) (Box 17)
  - Johnny Cash and the Tennessee Two - Original Golden Hits, vol. II - RCA, no date. (S143754) (Box 17)
- Box 18
  - Super Hits - vol. 18 performed by the Sir Echoes - Fantastic F, 1973. (MT8-211) (Box 18)
  - Hard Times for Lovers - Judy Collins - Elektra/Asylum Records, 1979. (ET-8171) (Box 18)
  - Liberace Sends You Love - ABC Records, 1974. (BR-8-3000) (Box 18)
  - Diana Ross & The Supremes "Anthology" vol. 2 - Motown, 1974. (M-11-794-NT vol. 2) (Box 18)
  - Don Ho's Greatest Hits - Don Ho & The Aliis - Warner Bros, 1969. (REP M8 6357) (Box 18)
  - Bill Black's Combo Plays the Greatest Hits - Zodiac, 1976. (ZL8-5006) (Box 18)